# Yunlin Li

Mobile: 07900918268, Email: ling428lyl@gmail.com,

GitHub: <a href="mailto:ling428lyl">ling428lyl</a> (github.com), Portfolio Website: <a href="https://yunlinli-portfolio-website.netlify.app/">https://yunlinli-portfolio-website.netlify.app/</a>

## **SUMMARY**

A versatile and creative game designer/developer skilled in Unity, Maya and related VR/AR technologies, with a foundation in Network Engineering and a Master's in Immersive Technologies. Demonstrated ability to integrate both creative and technical aspects of game design and game art within various experience in VR & AR development, game design & development, 3D modeling & animations and web development.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Bristol 09/2023-12/2024

Master of Science in Immersive Technologies (Virtual and Augmented Reality)

> Core Modules: Virtual Environment Design, Immersive Interaction and Audio Design, Augmenting the Real World, Immersive Games Design and Production.

Guangzhou University 09/2019-06/2023

Bachelor of Engineering in Network Engineering

Core Modules: Database Principles, Data Structures, Object Oriented Programming (C++), Web Application Technology, Software Engineering, etc.

#### SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

Skills: Unity, Maya, Procreate, RealityCapture, Photoshop, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vue.js, Node.js, C++.

Awards: Guangzhou University 3<sup>rd</sup> Prize Scholarship (2019-2020 & 2021-2022).

Language: Native in Cantonese & Mandarin; English (IELTS-7.0).

## PROJECT EXPERIENCE

VR Graffiti Stealth Game 06/2024-08/2024

- Designed all aspects of the game (e.g. mechanics, narratives and levels) with the other member.
- > Created different animations, poses and trigger logics of the VR hand models according to different interactions.
- Implemented UI design, spray cans interactions and the paint mechanic using VR techniques in Unity. Used Behaviour Tree to implement the AI behaviours.

#### **AR Application of Children Story Book**

02/2024-04/2024

Predicted Grade: 65

Grade: 88

- Designed the UI and Created the first scene of *The Gruffalo* story in Unity using AR techniques (e.g. tracking, rayeast, light estimation, etc.).
- ➤ Used RealityCapture to create the virtual 3D model of the character and created the animation in Maya.
- Ensured the scene cohesion and demonstrated the application with other teammates.

#### VR Zombie Survival Shooting Game

02/2024-04/2024

- Designed and implemented the game in Unity with teammates (version control and feature integration in GitLab).
- > Implemented the game tutorial and UI design. Created different animations, poses and trigger logics of the VR hand models according to different interactions.

#### **VR Symphonic Planets Interactive Experience**

02/2024-04/2024

- > Designed the realistic materials, particle effects of the element balls and set terrain generation in the main planet according to different elements in the game.
- Used different instruments to compose the soundtracks based on the traits of the element balls in the game.

#### Virtual Environment Design of a Tea Shop

10/2023-12/2023

- Took reference pictures and modelled a virtual environment in Maya, to accurately recreate a tea shop in Bristol.
- Modelled the furniture, decorations and plants, applied textures and designed lighting of the environment.

#### Campus lost and found mini-program design and implementation

01/2023-04/2023

- Understood relevant topics and research. Analysed feasibility and requirements of the system and designed the functional modules, interface and database.
- Implemented various functions (e.g. login, upload & post, classify, search, comment, etc.) of the mini-program and the backend management system using Vue.js, Node.js, MongoDB, JavaScript etc.

## **Creative Programming for Digital Media & Mobile Apps**

06/2022-08/2022

Online Course Organised by Goldsmiths, University of London

➤ Developed dynamic audiovisual applications, user experiences, and physics-based games integrating sound, graphics and interaction in Processing, using JavaScript and Box2D physics engine.

#### **INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE**

## **Agricultural Bank of China**

09/2022-10/2022

Front-end Development Intern

- Collaborated with team (version control in SVN) to complete an E-commerce management system based on Vue.js, discussed with the product manager to determine the project requirements and overall project design.
- Designed static webpages and programmed interfaces for front-end and back-end interactions, implemented and improved the functionality in the requirements and tested the project.

#### Guangdong Planning and Designing Institute of Telecommunications Co., Ltd

07/2022-09/2022

Front-end Development Intern

- Produced front-end pages (e.g. order management, product management, etc.).
- Used different JavaScript frameworks based on the current project (Vue and React), cooperated and communicated with the back-end personnel to conduct large-screen data visualisation and displayed the data dynamically, which improved the efficiency of business decision-making.

## **Tencent Holdings Limited**

02/2022-03/2022

Part-time Assistant in Platform and Content Group

- > Communicated with the supervisor to understand the business requirements and clarify job responsibilities.
- Assisted in optimising the algorithm efficiency. Conceptualised the problems into data structures with C++, simulated real-world data processing and designed algorithms to enhance computing efficiency.

#### **CREATIVE PRACTICE**

#### Design of the Guangzhou University Postgraduate Admission Letter

03/2022-04/2022

Designed and produced a creative work of postgraduate admission letter in Procreate and Photoshop, including the envelope based on the traits of the campus and the city culture.

#### Colour 60-day Challenge Vol.8

03/2022-05/2022

➤ Completed one colour painting each day in Procreate and Photoshop. Learnt about colour theories and analysed different photographers' works & masterpieces.